In the far distant future,
when cars are giving up their wheels in the changeover to air-cars,
there still exist fools...
who carry on a vanishing spirit of racing...
who carry on a vanishing spirit oi racing... And
the lead pack has entered the long, long pass.
And the lead pack
has entered the long, long pass.
In the meantime,
the relay units have begun...
...moving on to the water stop here.
Even after two interplanetary wars,
REDLINE's still as popular
as ever with the public.
This is the true ultimate race,
where anything goes.
My money's on Sonoshee.
You really like her, huh?
I put mine on Deguon.
The only rule is that racers must use retro-style engines...
You're kidding!
So'?
The only rule is that racers must use retro-style engines...
I can't.
You stink!
Instead of the currently mainstream anti-gravity engine.
You can squeeze 'm!
Once again, 2358 teams have entered from all over...
Who did you bet on'?
In pursuit of the title "The Fastest in Space.“
JP.
In pursuit of the title "The Fastest in Space."
No way'.!
In pursuit of the title "The Fastest in Space. ”
in pursuit of the title "The Fastest in Space."
Papa'. Where were you'?
Papa! Where were you?
149 teams qualified in the BLUELINE preliminary races
from their home worlds, Papa'. Where were you'?
149 teams qualified in the BLUELINE
preliminary races from their home worlds,
while 6 teams made it through the YELLOWLINE race.
Papa! This way! Hurry!
A battle for the last spot is now raging here at YELLOWLINE.
The venue for REDLINE is still under wraps.
We're all curious to see the result of viewers' request.
Once the winner of YELLOWLINE is determined,
REDLINE's venue will be announced.
Get around to the right.
Okay-
Our own relay unit Portal has
just arrived at the final relay point.
Papa! A Portal is here!
It's a Portal! Look!
Now, let's get back to the race
and see who's coming first.
Don't push me!
Papa! Get the camera, quick!
It's upside down, Papa!
Papa! The lens cap's on!
Wow! Did you see that?! So cool!
Only 50 klicks left in the Planet Dorothy YELLOWLINE.
Against everyone's expectations,
Cherry Boy Hunter Sonoshee McLaren's
hover jet is still the lead,
She's heading straight toward
the goal in Crab Sonoshee.
And there's the very first
REDLINE champion:
Captain-2-Block's
Captain the Classic in second.
Followed by the REDLINE regular,
Count Markdie and Spark in their Snake Head.
Coming up fourth is Lynchman's archenemy,
Psychoman & Lotten's Psycho Rod.
With these 4 leading the race,
the second group is coming up
14 seconds behind them.
From Planet Supergrass,
ruled by the Princess with magical powers,
Deguon's Fire Bird is leading the group.
Right behind her is Planet Dorothy's
own Bans Missile-EP4.
And bringing up the rear is
Sweet JP's Trans-Am.
The other racers are left way behind.
Looks like it's down to these seven.
Though I have my doubts about JP at this stage.
Oh, you got doubts?
Just trying to make things interesting here.
What do you announcers...
...know about racing?
JP's uncorked the nitro on the final stretch!
He's making a break for it!
He's broken away from the
second group on a rocket ride!
Crab Sonoshee is hanging on to the lead.
Look out!
JP's Trans-Am is on its tail!
Take this!
Look at those
fantastic moves from JP!
This has turned into one hell of a battle!
The crowds must be going wild.
Captain the Classic moves up on Crab Sonoshee.
Punk!
He held back till the last quarter, like you said.
He's the odds on favorite near the finish.
Everything's hunky dory, huh Frisbee?
If there's anyone who can
pull off a fix like this, it's JP.
None of these guys can beat him
at the YELLOWLINE.
That's what you say.
You don't think JP would
try to win this, do you?
Not a chance.
But if he wins, he qualifies for REDLINE.
You don't think he may just decide to go for it?
That won't happen. I can guarantee that.
You're becoming a nuisance,
Cherry Boy Hunter!
Crab Sonoshee hover jet takes a chance
by diving into the river:
You're not getting away!
I'll send you all to hell!
Here we go!
You know Frisbee, if JP wins,
the syndicate's gonna take a big hit.
Look, he isn't called Sweet JP for nothing.
Besides, he wouldn't risk going back in the joint.
Sweet JP, huh? I hope you're right.
Bids are locked.
And our position on JP?
All unloaded.
Good.
Now we'll see how your friendship with JP plays out.
Hold it, hold it...
Now!!
Overtaking Crab Sonoshee,
JP finally takes the lead!
Nobody can catch him now.
He's charging straight for
the finish line on nitro boost!
YES!
You guys aren't just amateurs.
You're total shit!
Shit racers!
Let's go.
Thank you!
Sonoshee McLaren won the
Planet Dorothy YELLOWLINE.
A new queen of racing is born!
And the ticket to REDLINE is hers.
Listen to the crowd!
This completes the lineup of racers for REDLINE.
And the venue for the big race
will be announced shortly.
Look.
What? You first.
No, you go.-
Look, just go first.
You go first.
That Trans-Am must cost a fortune.
You couldn't possibly put together a machine like that.
You knew exactly what you were getting into.
You're off the hook with your bondsman now.
That should cover your hospital bill and more.
I'd say it's a win-win.
Racers and mechanics gotta stick together.
You and I have
always made a good team.
Call me when you
wanna get back in the game.
We can make tons of money
as a team, you know.
What the fuck was that for?!
I changed my mind.
It's all yours.
What's this?
An attack of principles?
What about your bondsman?!
So I go back in.
Probably better off.
Whoa! What the hell?!
Hold it! Hold it!
JP! How do you feel about
going to REDLINE?
Sweet JP! How about
a big smile for our camera?
Hey! Leave me out of this!
No pictures!
Are you really going for the race?
Will you drop out?
What are you talking about?
I just blew the YELLOWLINE.
Right.
You mean you don't know?
Huh?
To replace the already declined...
KURUKURU=DAZA
and SHOTO=O-JIN,
the team Miki & Todoroki,
the winner of the Blue Line,
and JP who made a brilliant run at the
YELLOWLINE, have been nominated.
Seriously?
What?
They just announced
the next REDLINE's venue.
It'll be at Roboworld. Roboworld!
Roboworld?!
Roboworld?
My beloved people
of the M3 nebula!
I will not allow the REDLINE
to enter our Roboworld!
Shame on those REDLINE criminals
for disturbing the peace of our nebula!
Our Roboworld exists as
a symbol of peace for humanity.
I can never allow REDLINE
to enter this sacred place!
Any REDLINE outsiders
who invade our territory...
will be destroyed,
by any means necessary!
Come on, there's no way.
They just announced
a few minutes ago...
that the next REDLINE's
gonna be held at Roboworld.
I can't believe they're allowing this.
That's just it. They're not.
Thought so.
That's why KURUKURU=DAZA
and SHOTO=O-JIN dropped out.
I was gonna be in it for fun, you know?
There's no way I'm gonna race
while I get attacked by some army!
Good point.
I'm a racer now, not a soldier:
I've had enough of that shit.
I can't do it.
Roboworld is an important client
of my kingdom.
I'm not ready to give up
my life just yet.
So after the popularity poll,
the top 2 teams were picked.
I see...
JP, are you going?
Or will you drop out?
JP, please make a statement!
I take it back, Frisbee.
Fix up the Trans-Am, will you?
What?
So you're going, then?
Is that official, JP?
He won't.
Please give us a comment, JP! A simple yes or no!
Think twice before you say something.
Give me the camera.
Watch out, Roboworld! Here comes JP!
All right! He's in! JP's in! And there you
have it from JP who has qualified for REDLINE.
Oh goody! It's time for the festival of fools again!
I like rough sports every now and then.
PAROLE
SATELLITE EUROPASS
The ship is approaching Roboworld's satellite, Europass.
Please prepare for landing in your designated pod.
Wow! It's picking up speed.
Flaps... Flaps...
Where's the flaps button?
Is this a coffin or what?!
This is nothing but a serious act
of aggression against Roboworld!
Secretary Titan!
Si"
You must have something to report!
I just received a message from our scout vessels.
They identified a group of ships on Europass's surface.
Europass?
Yes.
The planet we donated to those pathetic refugees.
It's demilitarized under our treaty
with the M3 Nebula Federation.
That means our forces must tread very carefully there.
Besides, the refugees from
nearby sectors have drifted in...
and set up slums all over the place.
It's an ideal hideout for REDLINE racers.
This is what we get
for being so generous!
They have the audacity to claim it's
by the viewers' request.
Don't they know we can't put
our military secrets at risk?
There's no way we'd allow
a stupid race in such a sacred place!
Mr. President.
Are you all right, sir?
Mr. President!
What?
You're not going to stand by and let them pass, are you?
I make the rules on this planet!
All those affiliated with REDLINE are
guilty and deserve to be hanged!
As president, I'll take full responsibility!
Because I represent justice.
The entire universe is in need of strong leadership,
and Roboworld stands
heroically by its principals!
Colonel Volton!
Si"
Are you ready to shed your blood for justice?
Sir! More than ready, sir!
Good! Fight with your life for ultimate justice!
Thank you, sir!
Hey, you!
Hey, I'm talking to you!
Don't you ignore me!
Buy a ticket for REDLINE, will ya?
Don't ignore me!
You have money, don't you?
How about I give you a discount?
What happened there?
Get off me.
What happened?
Stop it! Sorry to disappoint,
but I'm not here to watch.
Useless! You're so totally useless to us!
Ahh...fuck!
Wait!
1, 2, s, 4...
Next!
What is this?
You're sure about the exchange rate?
Just about right. Next!
Just about? What the heck is that?
You need to take money more serious...
You're annoying!
Right here.
What?
Need some smokes.
Got money?
Sure. I just cashed in.
Give me as many as this will get.
Here.
What, is this it?
It's already open.
This ain't right.
Hey, Grandma!
Money needs to be taken...
Don't like it? Then leave it.
Just leave it and walk away!
Huh?
Whoops.
Whoa! Whoa!
View's clear!
Good. Let's roll!
Nice!
These antigravity engines aren't bad!
Yeah, not bad at all!
Done.
Oh, it's you, JP.
This planet is really something, huh?
What did you expect?
This place gets flotsam from all over the galaxy.
It's hard for the idea of service to sink in.
How are you holding up?
Alright, I guess... Ouch!
Yeah, I can see that.
Ow... Ow...
I got an attaché case from Frisbee.
It was stuffed with cash.
Yeah, it's for fixing up
the Trans-Am.
He used to drop everything
to work on your machine.
He sure has changed.
Like you, me, and everything else.
Cigs cost more and good junk joints
are harder to find.
So, where's my Trans-Am?
You really did it this time,
you ingrate.
What were you thinking,
using the nitro twice?
You got a death wish?
I'll need three caps for the REDLINE.
Three?!
Hey, watch it, Pops!
This is a totally different level
than the YELLOWLINE.
I'm gonna need an edge, won't I?
Then get your machine armed up.
You know that
anything goes at REDLINE.
I can get you armed up good.
REDLINE's a race, not a war.
Keep that crap off of my machine.
I see you're as stupidly soft
as your nickname implies.
Don't call me that!
In the REDLINE, you can attack or
interfere with the others any way you want.
You're behind the times
by trying to play fair.
Behind the times, huh?
30 years in this business and
I still got my chops. Not bad, huh?
I clean up good with all
the trades I get at the race.
A little fun on the side wouldn't hurt, either.
A little fun.
Listen, JP.
If you want a stove that'll stand up to 3 caps of juice,
you're talking a redesign from scratch.
If you don't want to use weapons,
all I can do is to get you
a new engine and custom parts.
I wish I could do more.
Hey, you listening to me?
Frisbee can handle
the redesigning and tune-up.
You're joking.
Huh? Why?
When was the last time
you two worked as a team?
Stop it.
Frisbee's not legit anymore.
Cut it out!
He's sold out. He's no good!
Talking about the fix?
He's not the same man. You know that, right?
Helping an ingrate like you is no big deal,
but getting mixed up with that scum is another story.
Racers and mechanics
gotta stick together.
You and I make a good team.
Always have.
Hey, Frisbee.
Took you long enough.
I may be a scum,
but I still got the touch, you know.
Don't judge a man's skill by his character.
So, you've also learned to
sneak around now, Frisbee?
Relax, Pops.
If I didn't have the touch,
I wouldn't still be here.
Nobody's worried about your touch.
The old man's on board.
I didn't agree to anything.
Hey, quit that!
I guess I'll leave it to the two of you now.
Hey! Where are you going?
The old man will get a new engine.
Frisbee'll take care of the redesign and mods.
I'll do my job when I put my butt behind the wheel.
Until then, I'll leave everything to you pros.
Like the old days.
He think he's cool or something?
What do you want?
This ain't your seat, punk!
You want some?!
Oh, a comb...
Don't scare me, you fool!
I see you're having a full house today, waiter.
I'm the manager, you jerk!
And enough with the wisecracks!
The place is deserted.
Just pick a table and settle down, will ya?
Okay, okay.
Sorry about that, Miss.
He won't bother you anymore,
so don't worry.
Here's your soup spaghetti
a la Europass lobster.
Looks great!
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
You're breaking the dress code, Manager.
Oh, no! How embarrassing!
What are you doing?
Nothing.
No, seriously.
Excuse me. I'm JP.
JP?
Are you gonna eat that?
Huh?
What's this?
Give me a break...
Mind if I join you?
Sorry, I'm waiting for someone.
Bummer.
I remember now!
You're that guy from the YELLOWLINE.
You're going to REDLINE
as a substitute, right?
What do you want?
I thought I'd check you out
since you're going, too.
Come again?
She saw my underpants...
Winning the YELLOWLINE with a hover engine...
was so cool that I wanted to
check out the racer for myself.
And the verdict?
Verdict? Well...
I see an engine geek with no interest in men.
Bingo.
Wheels are my only love.
I've known nothing but racing since I was a kid.
So, you're one of those sad types who
can't make any human friends, huh?
Meaning what?
Why don't you just go now?
My dad was a racer.
We owned a junk joint.
We used to build our own
machines to enter races.
I see.
It was the most natural thing to do...
What's that?
Steamlight. Isn't it pretty?
My Dad gave it to me on my 7th birthday.
So this is a steamlight, huh?
I've never seen one before.
They say when burned as fuel,
it releases 100 times more energy
than gold nitro.
No kidding.
This is my first time seeing real steamlight, too.
An energy source with unlimited capacity.
No man can handle that
amount of power, though.
You know a lot, don't you?
Oh, how do you do.
I'm Shinkai.
Pleased to meet you.
Aren't you gonna eat that?
Hexagonal worm spaghetti soup.
It's so good!
Please have some.
Hooray!
May I perhaps taste some of you as well tonight?
Yummy time!
She would have been mine
if you hadn't interrupted.
Mr. Substitute.
Call me a reserve.
You guys are racers, right?
I saw you on the news.
I'm a racer myself, you know.
Though I must say I'm more known as a mechanic.
I have a partner named Trava.
Trava?
Let me go!
Stop trashing the place! Take it outside!
Trava!
Your partner?
The one getting beaten up, yes.
Which one is that?
Hey, that hurt!
You started it.
Shit! Here he goes!
It's your fault, damn it!
You betrayed the army.
Is the tough guy crying?
That's Little Deyzuna.
He used to be in the army with us.
He becomes impossibly strong when he cries.
Having a race on Roboworld!
You're just doing that to make me suffer!
That's bullshit!
It's nothing personal and you know it!
Liar!
Hm. More weirdoes on the scene.
Well, if it ain't Machine Head Tetsuzin himself.
That's really Machine Head?
Mr. REDLINE.
The fastest man in the galaxy.
Outta my way.
Don't order me around!
I said, outta my way!
You think you can order me around?
I'm just telling you to move.
That's an order, you moron!
Fine, if you won't move,
I'll go around you.
That's what you get
when you mess with me!
To hell with the race!
Sonoshee!
This way!
What?
Looks like Roboworld forces.
You're a hard man to find,
Little Deyzuna.
Colonel Volton!
You weren't ordered
to leave the base.
I told you to stay put, didn't I?
Look what you did!
Thanks for coming here personally...
to deal with your insubordinate
subordinate, Col. Volton.
Stay there!
This is a demilitarized zone.
We won't stand for this.
So what?
I said so what?
Are Roboworld soldiers
hard of hearing?
Oh, I can hear you fine.
I just don't need your permission.
Doesn't matter. I got what I came for.
Oh, yes, and I have orders to
use force on the day of the race.
Seriously?!
Volton's Hell Troops have been
ordered into action?
The president generously offered
his presence at your silly race.
You should try to be good targets
for our troops in return.
I suppose having your heads can wait.
Hey, you!
Don't try something stupid.
The air in here's kinda stuffy
since you guys walked in.
Beat it.
You've got seven guns
pointed at you.
Nice. That'll solve my...
Ow.
Ow!
That hurts...
How's your head?
I'll live.
What were you thinking?
Those bastards were really trying my patience.
Couldn't help it.
You got your plans all
screwed up by them, too.
I guess you're right.
Thanks for this.
You really are sweet, aren't you?
It's a stupid nickname for the fans,
Cherry Boy Hunter Sonoshee McLaren.
Cherry Boy...what's that?
Don't you read the papers?
That nickname of yours made quite a headline.
That's stupid!
Don't look at me.
What was that for?
Why the sour face?
Cherry Boy Hunter...
Can I ask you something?
What?
Why do you race?
Why do you?
Me? Not much to tell.
Then don't ask me.
Sorry.
C'mon! Out with it!
I mean...
it's really no big deal.
Really.
Is that so?
You need more muscles if
you wanna take those bastards.
Good night now.
G'night.
Hey, you dropped this!
Oh, well.
Go faster! Go!
Alright! Go for it!
That was close!
Is she okay?
You did great!
You drive like the wind!
You gave it all you have.
Just forget about it.
I'm gonna race in the REDLINE someday!
What?
I bust my ass off for it everyday.
I can't afford to waste my time like this!
I'm not like you amateurs
who are all talk and no action.
Why don't you quit watching and
get down here with the rest of us?
Wow...
I bet she doesn't remember.
JP!
I'm telling you,
I can't work with this jerk.
Why?
Your pal here says
he doesn't like the engine I got.
You sure about him?
It's REDLINE!
We need something bigger,
or else we're just wasting our time.
We're talking about the race here!
A man is driving!
This guy's talking about
a goddamn TRZ Airmaster, JP!
Seriously?!
Go ahead, laugh!
It's crap!
Powerful, but unstable as hell.
A four cycle TRZ Airmaster!
All it needs is a dose of
Frisbee magic and it'll be fine.
Like hell!
Besides, JP's driving it.
You think he hasn't got what it takes?
You are the only one I have trouble trusting.
Who do you think you are?
Showing up with all that money,
then you start bossing me around!
Pops! Showing up with all that money,
Just get him what he wants.
Huh? What was that?
Get him what he needs.
You're gonna get killed!
As far as the design goes,
Frisbee's in charge.
We're a team, right?
Ha! It's all in the past.
You know how long it'll take to get one of those monsters?
It's your job to get what
we need in time for the race.
You're in charge of getting us the engine parts.
Some things just can't be done.
Pops... Please.
Let me race in his machine.
Fine, you fool...
It'll cost you double though.
Thanks, Pops. I owe you one.
TWO DAYS TO REDLINE
Fast, huh?
Not as many racing as I expected.
Guys with money like to
keep it quiet at the private tracks.
Yeah. This is the place for the struggling racers.
Don't worry. Looks like the
engine will make it in time.
He always comes through,
even on impossible jobs like this.
That's our Pops.
I talked to lnuki, by the way.
Same drill as before.
Stay in the rear till the third quarter
to get your odds down.
Then make your move in the last quarter.
Say...
Once I'm in the Trans-Am's seat,
I'm the boss, right?
I'd rather find another way
to pay for the engine.
You may get a spare engine,
but not a spare life.
We really have no choice.
We're all in this together.
Come what sparks or potato chip
crumbs that may fall on us.
ROBOWORLD MINERAL EXTRACTION SITE
That's it for today!
Let's go place our REDLINE bets.
Yeah!
ROBOWORLD ILLEGAL UNDERGROUND BETTING PARLOR
Bet on #4. It's the current favorite to win.
Okay, gimme 100 on #4.
How about you?
I'll take 150 on Gori Rider.
You sure? He always comes in fifth.
It won't hurt.
50 on #2 please.
Don't be stingy. Be bold!
50's fine.
I'll take 300 on JP.
You're betting on a long shot, huh?
The odds'll be 25,000 to 1.
I know.
What the hell?!
What's happening?
Disperse at once!
Shut up!
Give me money!
This is a violation of the law.
Next up is today's segment featuring Crab Sonoshee.
Her new engine can prevent a missile
lock-on by minimizing its heat output.
As you can see on this thermograph chart,
it's much lower than her old engine.
It can now avoid
a missile's heat sensor.
My butt's on camera!
Looks like Crab Sonoshee's engine
mods are going well for REDLINE.
The man of sonic speed.
Since his first win at the fourth REDLINE,
this invincible king's been at the top for 20 years.
The machine integrated racer
who keeps altering himself...
along with his machine “God Wing.”
The irrefutable champion of REDLINE!
King of kings, Mr. REDLINE:
Machine Head Tetsuzin!
Good evening all.
I'm Machine Head Tetsuzin.
Well, for me... How shall I put it?
I'd say I'm in a different league
compared to the others.
'Cause in my case,
I'm a part of my machine.
For the others,
it's "Me and my wheels."
But in my case,
it's "I am my wheels," you see?
He can't underestimate his rivals, though.
The royal family's Boiboi and
Bosbos make their return,
with Princess Supergrass,
the last heir to magical superpowers.
This time around,
they've sealed off their magic.
The carefree beauty pair - Super Boins.
Hi there! I'm the super sexy
and gorgeous racer, Boiboi.
I don't know about that,
but oh well... I'm Bosbos.
We are Super Boins!
Wanna see my specialty?
I can make all kinds of faces.
SEE?
Well? Impressive, huh?
I can make funny faces, too.
So cute!
Now you're creeping me out.
So? What do you say?
Dear Princess!
We are going to win for sure!
Planet Supergrass' racing singing super idol.
Here's their new single, Zooming Gears!
And how can we forget this amazing pair?
Heel hero of Alsatia.
The strongest, fastest bounty hunters!
The Mad Brothers - Lynchman and Johnny Boya!
We're Lynchman and Johnny Boya,
the bounty hunters.
Don't tell me you don't know!
We've never failed catching our targets ever,
'cause we're fast.
That bastard Machine Head
beat us in the last REDLINE,
but with our new machine, it's gonna
be totally different from five years ago!
Wait and see! We'll pay you back
double for last time!
Don't wet your pants, suckers!
Lynchman's best fight #7,
now on sale!
What the hell?
REDLINE EVE
Looking good.
A test car for the image training.
I installed the engine
from an old TRZ Airmaster.
No kidding!
You should be able to get a feel with this.
May I?
Of course.
This is great!
This will do.
Oh! Crab Sonoshee!
Hey, everyone! After his dramatic
crash landing in the YELLOWLINE,
JP's done it again during his latest test run.
After crashing at 300 kph,
he was miraculously uninjured.
A showdown between rivals!
It's the day before the YELLOWLINE
which saw Miki and Todoroki qualify,
and a policeman relentlessly chases speeding cars.
He makes a bull-charge at the BLUELINE champs,
who made it to REDLINE
as reserves.
Dirty Policeman Hamesh Frini,
a.k.a. "Gori Rider"!
The tape shows excessive force
in dealing with a speed violation!
I'll bust them cocky racers
who dare to challenge me...
by any means necessary.
You got that?!
A comment please, Gori Rider.
A police officer, who should be a
moral paragon, engaged in adultery?
Would you care to comment on
your affair with Ms. Yang-Sue?
Shut up!
The vengeful wild pair
from the shining blue planet,
Miki and Todoroki!
With racing charisma that turns
any road into a race course,
they swear to take revenge in the REDLINE.
Gori Rider, you mother fucker!
It's finally here, JP!
Can't get any better than this baby.
That 80 mm thick cylinder block
can give you 35,000 horsepower.
The last Airmaster.
Wow...
It's not a dream.
We finally got it...
Of course.
Thought I couldn't pull it off?
It's a great engine
with extraordinary power.
It's up to you now, Frisbee.
Right. I'll have this in
the Trans-Am by morning.
With a beefed up stove,
it's good for three loads.
Relax, Pops.
I'm putting my reputation at stake here.
Must be a pre-race party
going on at Roboworld,
The goddess may see those.
Where're you going at this hour?
Gotta go.
Where the hell is he going?
It's the night before the REDLINE.
No idea.
Well, do what you will.
ROBOWORLD UNDERGROUND POWER RELAY STATION
The walls are 800 mm thick cosmo titanium.
Fire the shock-breaker!
They're in! Fucking Robopolice!
Trespassers detected.
Come down from the walk immediately.
You got no business here! Get lost!
Hostile intent detected.
Cease your resistance and surrender.
Shut up!
Over my dead body!
Shoot the Runners till they're down!
You bastard!
Stay the hell down!
What is it?
Disgruntled workers have attacked
our main power station,
so we switched to auxiliary power.
Large-scale weapons are disabled
till the power gets restored.
Damn them!
Rest assured, Mr. President.
We have a secret weapon for those
who enter our atmosphere.
A giant A.l. we've been
developing over the years.
A solar system integrated satellite
weapon unit we call...
...the hyper-disintegreator cannon!
Please take a look.
Hey, Lynchman.
What?
Why did the REDLINE Commission
put us up to this?
If the hyper-disintegrator
blasts everyone to hell,
there won't be any race.
That means no betting.
I see.
Get in.
That won't be good for the fat cats.
You know how much money is riding on this?
No idea.
Enough to buy out a couple of planets.
Oh, wow!
Besides, it's gonna be
great publicity for them.
REDLINE's odds'll go up,
and so will their margins.
I get it.
So this is our target for today?
You got it!
The main power station's system was attacked...
...by pro-REDLINE guerrillas
consisting of low-level workers.
As a result, the RED-RACERS...
are now safe from
heavy ground-based weaponry.
Roboworld officials are currently
working on corrective measures.
According to government sources,
the malfunction of the power system...
...occurred late last night.
When the Robopolice arrived...
What's your name?
JP?
Where did you get that?
Weird name.
I'm Sonoshee.
Sonoshee.
With REDLINE just a day away,
we should keep our eyes on the
racers trying to enter Roboworld.
For this non-stop road race
in the military exercise base,
each driver's course pick will hold the key.
We've been profiling the
REDLINE racers every evening.
On the eve of the big race,
we feature JP,
who's entering only because
another racer dropped out.
Like Lynchman, who's notorious
for his rough play,
JP has a dark past of his own.
According to our research,
this man with a nickname of “Sweet JP“
was indeed a race-fixing
specialist in the past.
What the hell?
This is REDLINE, a festival awaited by
young and old every 5 years.
We need to make sure all concerned
parties are aware of the fact that...
Lucky for me.
It's still running.
REDLINE FINALS DAY
What was that?
I think it's the Supergrass' scout vessel.
The army of that wicked wizard princess, eh?
So, they've teamed up with
the REDLINE now, have they?
Easy does it, easy...
Easy, easy...
Slop!
Too bad you have to race without a test run.
I'll be fine.
JP!
Yeah?
You know the drill, right?
What I know is that it's my show now.
What's that red smoke?
Ta-d ah!
Nice work, Princess.
Piece of cake.
PLANET SUPERGRASS, GRASS HALL
Now, all we have to do is to wait for the start.
We're going there to win, alright?
I've just received word
that Supergrass' Red Angels...
have successfully marked the
finish line by the Roboworld Tower.
That's our princess!
I guess she made it.
Of course.
She's the only one who can use remote magic.
We must make her proud.
Morning, Sonoshee!
Looks like you're mad at me.
Not really...
We're rivals now anyway.
Once we're on the race track,
friendship won't count.
I guess you're right.
Uh huh.
Sonoshee.
Three minutes to drop zone.
Good luck, then.
You see the transport ship?
Yes, Mr. President.
Let's say the line marked by
our HQ is the finish line.
At 800 km west above the expected
start line at Knockout Tower,
we detected an energy reading
from a hyperdimensional drive.
Hyperdimensional drive?
How dare they violate our airspace
using a navigation method...
that's only supposed
to exist in theory!
I'll teach those RED-RACERS a lesson!
Titan! Arm the disintegrator cannons!
Yes, sir!
Bought your ticket yet?
Hey! You put it all on Sonoshee.
Yeah! Sonoshee's my girl.
You're the man!
Give me those pork buns!
Only three left.
Fine.
Hey, you! You betting or not?
Not yet. I'm waiting for the final odds.
Hot!
Ew! What a mess!
You're supposed to eat them in one bite.
Okay guys, last call!
Anyone who wants to buy in,
step up now.
One minute to the start!
I'm closing now!
Give me JP!
One minute to drop point.
All racers, please prepare for the drop.
Deploying apogee motors
on hyper-disintegrator cannons.
95% energy level.
Stand by on firing button.
Please put on your light shield, sir.
Entering drop zone.
We have an energy reading
on the transport ship.
It's out of hyperdimensional drive.
Put it on the monitor.
Open fire upon visual contact.
Aye, aye, sir.
Hyper-disintegrator cannons, fire!
Firing!
What's wrong?
Why aren't they firing?
We have a malfunction.
What?! That's unacceptable!
Good morning, all you lucky fans
gathered here today.
After five years of waiting,
it's the day of the big race!
We're broadcasting live to the cosmos
for all you crazy fans out there!
The Red-Machines are being
airdropped to start the race...
and heading straight toward Knockout Tower.
If you're looking for a long shot,
here's your man!
JP with his trademark ducktail.
His odds are a whopping
25,000 to 1!
What's going on with that hair?
But his machine's just as impressive.
You see every kind of design
imaginable in this race,
but I don't think anyone's
ever modified a car like JP.
Looks great. Sweet dedication
from the sweet man.
Dedication? Maybe.
Or maybe his hair is affecting his brain.
Calling the race is me,
the rattle-king Void Do.
And here for commentary is
former RL champ, Mr. Minerva Hanness.
Stay tuned!
Damn that REDLINE...
Mr. President, let my Voltan Corps
take over from here.
All right.
Show them what you've got!
Soldiers of the Voltan Corps!
Our time has come!
Those racers will be approaching
from three directions.
Split into three groups to counter them!
Volton Corps, move out!
Yes, sir!
I'm going down! Bye-bye!
Here comes God Wing followed by Busties!
Speed Master and Semimaru are right behind.
Here goes!
God Wing makes a splash landing,
immediately going for a counterattack!
What do you do now, Super Boins?
They're blazing away!
You can't counterattack unless
you make a swift landing, first!
Lynchman's gunning for Sonoshee.
Will he catch up?
Johnny! Shoot a Sidewinder
into Crab Sonoshee.
Okay!
Jesus, I'm burning!
That bastard!!
What the hell?!!
Huh?
Fools!
Ow, hoooottt!!
YEEEE-HAAAA!
No way!
Oh, no!
Not bad, Colonel Volton.
Thank you, sir.
What?
I see.
Sir, I just got word we have another problem.
What now?
Observe, please.
REDLINE's broadcast ratings.
82% of the broadcast satellites
in the M3 Nebula...
are uplinked to that
mothership as a terminal...
and are beaming live coverage of
the REDLINE to the entire galaxy.
In other words,
every secret military asset
and facility on Roboworld...
Smash those racers
before they reach...
zone 7X where
Funky Boy is sleeping.
Funky Boy must not be awakened.
He's still a baby
barely out of the womb.
He needs more time
to learn to obey.
Payback time!
Suckers!
Good job, engine three!
Get a load of this!
Crab Sonoshee's bravely
charging up the slope!
Bold move!
She may be able
to take the short cut,
but Lynchcar and the Trans-Am
have to go around.
Johnny! I see the dam!
Here we go!
I see you, Lynchman!
Finally caught up, Cherry Boy Hunter?
I thought you'd retired.
You wish!
Don't celebrate yet!
Yes! Now we're even!
You're making this interesting,
Sonoshee McLaren!
Trava...
Regret leaving me behind in the army?
Captain Deyzuna!
What?
We've spotted a moving target
5 klicks to the west.
Looks like a RED-RACER.
Okay, all vehicles,
move onto the target!
Rogen
This one's mine.
I'm gonna rip his head off!
That weasel!
He thinks he can beat me?
I've been waiting for this
a long time, Trava!
What do you want, Deyzuna?
My sand-biker's gonna
whip your sorry ass!
In your dreams,
you pathetic little shit!
Come and get me!
Now let's check out what JP's up to.
He's finally approaching the dam
way behind the others.
I think it's time for JP to retire.
Yeah, really.
The engine and the machine's
out of balance! Friggin' Frisbee...
What's wrong, JP?
Get her up to speed and you're in the clear.
Don't be afraid to use the gold nitro.
Never thought I'd need this so soon.
Whoa, boy! GO!
He's skipping across!
Do you see that?
I don't believe it!
Skipping! Do you see this?!
You gotta hand it to him.
JP's Trans-Am is impressive.
He's still way behind the rest, though.
You're late, Frisbee.
How's your friend doing so far?
JP's holding the last place as we planned,
so his odds will stay low.
He'll make his move in the last quarter,
get his odds up, then he loses.
Same as in the YELLOWLINE.
No problem.
I'm still worried that
he may wanna win the race.
That will cost me a great deal, you know.
There's no guarantee, is there?
You can relax.
There won't be any surprises.
I guarantee that.
Noooooo!
Stop picking on us!
Oh, no!
I've had it!
Let's roll!
Hi!
Coochy-coochy-coo.
What's going on, Big Deyzuna?!
Two planes were down before I knew it.
So you lost a couple of planes.
No big deal!
Use your head!
Si"
Dr. Sabose! Quit playing around
with those pervs and tits!
Wipe out the racers in
the southern sector already!
Si"
Little Deyzuna! Who said you could
leave the unit to be in the REDLINE?
Sorry, sir! I'll do my best.
Get back in formation
and corner them to Zone 7X!
Are you reading me,
Little Deyzuna?
Colonel Volton, please!
Don't...
Don't let this punk make a fool of me.
Stop raving and get a hold of yourself!
I repeat once more.
Get back in formation
and chase them to Zone 7X!
That's an order from your commander!
I'm afraid I can't take that order, sir.
I'm entering the race.
Have you lost your mind?
You'll be court-martialed and shot!
Colonel Voltan...
I know the risk, but I must do this.
I promise victory!
No! I can't allow that! Deyz...
Colonel Volton! Are you going
to just stand by and watch?
Certainly not, Mr. President!
Attention, all soldiers of Roboworld!
All units, scramble!
Intercept all the RED-RACERs in Zone 7X!
You said all units, Colonel Voltan?
You heard me!
Send out all units!
All racers are converging at
the minefield in Zone 7X.
God Wing takes the lead
in the northern sector,
followed by Super Boins.
From southern sector
comes Crab Sonoshee!
Trava's Speed Master is
coming from the central sector,
with Little Deyzuna hot on his tail.
Speed Master's faster than
the detonators on those mines!
We just got some new footage.
Gori Rider's burrowing underground.
The Miki/Todoroki team
is running right behind him.
It may be a shortcut,
but speed-wise? I'm not sure.
Ouch! You think we've cleared 7X by now?
Probably. Let's get out of here
and take them down!
All right!
Let's do it, Miki!
Go get them, Todoroki!
GUTS AND GLORY!
You sure about waking it up?
XXXXXXXpoint (BASE 7x) - UNDERGROUND
XXXXXXXpoint (BASE 7X) - UNDERGROUND
Yeah. The bioweapon asleep
in Roboworld's untouchable area,
a.k.a. "Funky Boy."
We have to count on him
to fight Volton's troops.
Guts and glory! Guts and glory!
We're coming out!
Guts and glory!
There! Miki and Todoroki are making their move!
They've taken the lead!
Yes, Miki! We're in the lead!
Mine!
Looks like JP's made it to Zone 7X somehow.
What do you mean "somehow"?
Frisbee.
You do know this is business?
Of course I do.
Huh?!
Look, flying carriers!
I see they've decided to
send in Air-Destroyers.
Uh-oh!
Colonel Volton's getting serious.
He kicked me!
There's no end to them!
Ouch, ouch!
Lynchman!
Johnny, come closer!
Okay!
Todoroki!
Time to use the thunderbolt!
Rotate 120 degrees!
Guts and glory!
Shit, I missed!
We did it!
Launch flares!
That should teach them a lesson.
Those racers are as good as dead.
There's no need for any further attack.
Mr. President.
Did you think I'd stop now?
You can't afford to
take pity on that scum.
All right, then.
Damn, I can't break it!
Yes, you can!
Smash it with your rage!
What is this place?!
I'm coming to get you, Sonoshee.
What the...?!
That's a bioweapon!
Isn't that against the
peace treaty, Mr. Minerva?
I have a feeling we're not
supposed to be seeing this.
How can Funky Boy be...?!
I don't believe this!
Mr. President, Funky Boy
will destroy Roboworld.
Besides that, that giant bioweapon
is a clear violation of...
the M3 Nebula Peace Treaty,
and there are no scapegoats to pin this on!
We must take measures immediately!
You must make a decision, sir!
Mr. President!
Mr. President, we have the
hyper-disintegrator cannons back on line.
They'll be ready to fire
as soon as charging completes.
Agghhh...Hail the President!
Target Funky Boy!
He's out of control!
Yes, sir.
Target's set.
We can fire at any time.
All right.
Take him down in one shot!
Yes, sir.
Give me the command.
Fire the hyper-disintegrator cannons!
Firing!
Princess!
Excellent!
We wiped them out clean.
Energy discharge, complete.
Now recharging.
This can't be happening.
Are they really dead?
I don't believe this.
They actually used
hyper-disintegrator cannons.
It looks like everyone's
been wiped out.
That bastard planted something!
Sonoshee, you alright?
JP.
You okay, Captain Sabose?
I'm okay.
How many planes are left?
18, including the ones that got damaged.
16 sand-bikers left in another unit.
The crossjet unit's been wiped out
I see... The RED-RACERS
are in equally bad shape.
Wait for Colonel Volton's orders.
Roger.
C'mon, Sonoshee. Winning the
REDLINE's your dream, right?
I'm only halfway there.
I didn't get to see the finish line.
I'll show you. Not much room,
but you don't mind, do you?
The machine's gonna be too heavy.
You can't win.
Yes, I will.
We'll win this together!
That's sweet, JP,
but I have to ask you something.
Kinda busy right now!
No. I need to ask you now.
Fine!
Have you been arrested
for fixing a race?
Yeah.
What happened?
It was a Yellow MAX series 8 years ago.
Our team was on a hot winning streak.
Frisbee decided to hook up
with the mafia,
so he could get a
better engine and parts.
I entered the race
with his life on the line...
...and I lost.
After that, he desperately needed the money.
But there's a sting operation
against the lnuki gang.
They found stuff pointing to Frisbee.
He was trapped.
That friggin' Frisbee's gonna get JP killed!
So you went to prison for him.
He believed in me and
risked his life so I could race.
I always owe him for that.
Then we'll just have to pay him back
by winning the REDLINE.
You're gonna help me?
If you help me make
my dream come true.
Of course.
This is his regeneration function.
There must have been
some pieces of him left.
Secretary Titan!
Finish him off with the hyper-disintegrator cannons!
Negative. We need another
two hours to recharge it.
Where's Volton now?
I never thought I'd see this day.
Is it ready?
Yes, it's ready!
Can we control it?
With your skill, no problem.
You just like the idea of
getting new data, don't you?
Very well. Proceed.
Oh, no...Princeeeess!
This feels great! Wonderful!
I can feel the power!
Let's get out of here, Shinkai!
Okay!
All right! Gori-police custom rider!
You morons! The RED-RACERS
are running again.
Go after them, now!
Yes, sir!
We should get going.
This is the machine
your friend tuned up?
Yeah.
You ready?
Frisbee! With the beefed up stove you gave me,
Sonoshee and I will blast to the top!
Your friend has done well.
Yes.
It's time we wrapped this up.
We're in third.
The odds are looking up.
That should give us enough.
No point in getting greedy
and ending up in the hole, Frisbee.
Time to detonate the bomb.
Wait till JP grabs the lead, please.
You promised me!
Then here's a check!
Double what you got for
the YELLOWLINE race. Take it!
We're running out of time.
I'm paying both you and JP enough money.
What're you complaining about?
Gimme the detonator!
I want to see this race to the end.
To see us- No...
I want to see him win!
Sorry, Frisbee.
Nothing personal.
It's just business.
I don't wanna hurt you.
Just hand me the damn thing.
Over my dead body!
Suit yourself. You're dead!
BYE-bye!
Pops... Why are you here?
I'll keep this with me for now.
Got that?!
I didn't come here
to save you!
But a team mechanic's
gotta see the race through.
The driver, the mechanic,
and the junk dealer...
Those three make a team, right?
God Wing in the lead
is struggling to take control.
He sustained quite a bit
of damage this time around.
Hey! Clear the way!
Machine Head!
Quit tearing up the road!
I'm having a ball!
The outside course is clear!
We can't get there at this speed.
There!
Go for it!
You're here.
Finally caught up with you.
You got the guts to use
the steamlight, Sonoshee?
Huh? That's the same as yours...
As a courtesy to
stubborn racers like you,
I won't beat you just yet!
Bring it on!
Behold!
The platinum nitro charge!
And there it is!
Machine Head's Platinum nitro charge!!
The only man to master the steamlight.
Looks like the king's gonna win again!
Hey, Sonoshee!
We made a deal.
Make my dream come true!
Second spot is mine!
Think you can get me?!
That fool!
He's using steamlight?!
No man can handle that!
You can do it, JP!
Seriously?
Search me.
Ow... Hooott!!
Trying to be funny, huh?
Let's see what he's got.
Let's roll, Todoroki!
Guts and glory!
Sorry, Deyzuna. Time's up.
Let's go, Shinkai!
Here we come!
Don't leave me!
No way.
We'll never catch up with them.
Hold on a minute, Mr. Minerva!
Huh?
The finish line's on top
of the Dest Tower, isn't it?
No one can climb up the wall to reach the line!
What'll they do?
Princess, what's...?
Watch and see.
What the...?!
Check this out!
The REDLINE mothership has warped out
beneath the Dest Tower...
and became the final straightway!
You see it now?
The final straightway has
been joined to the finish line!
Ugh... Sonoshee...
Let's do it!
JP's moving up like a bullet!
What's going on?
Unbelievable!
This is unbelievable!
I'm gonna win.
I'm the king of kings!
You know what that means, JP?
It means victory belongs to me!
I'm gonna win.
I've got a goddess at my side!
Here they come!
Here come JP and Sonoshee!
I see it!
JP! You need an edge
to win the REDLINE!
You don't deserve to win this race!
Goddamn it! I need something
to juice this thing up...!
Frisbee! ls there anything?!
There's nothing left!
Whoa! JP's engine has blown!
It's blown!
But wait...
He's picking up speed somehow.
Victory's mine, JP!
JP!
Sonoshee!
It's JP and Sonoshee!
They're the winners!
JP and Sonoshee! JP and Sonoshee
came in top at the finish line!
JP! JP!
Sonoshee! Sonoshee!
He's done it!
Interesting...
Oh... That's beautiful.
Sonoshee.
I love you.
I love you, too, JP.